- 웬일이야?
- 기타를 두고 갔어
-What's up?
-I left my guitar here.
알았어
Okay. No problem.
자, 여깄어
Okay. Here you go.
- 왜?
- 나랑 같이 놀래?
-What?
-You want to hang out or something?
지금은 안 돼
You caught me at a bad time.
- 챈들러랑...
- 맞았어
-Are you and Chandler..?
-Exactly.
- 연주해줄까?
- 아니
-Can I play for you?
-No.
피비, 웬일이야?
Hey, Pheebs, what's up?
재미있는 질문이네, 챈들러 빙
You ask an intriguing question,
Chandler Bing.
맙소사! 마사지를 받아?
나한텐 못하게 했잖아
Oh, my God! You're getting a massage?
You never let me massage you.
피비, 이유가 있어
Phoebe, I can explain.
실은...
You see..
젠장, 거짓말이 안 나와
God, I gotta get better at lying.
마사지 싫어한댔잖아
You said you hate massages.
우표 사고 세탁물 찾고
피비가 못 들어오게 해라
Buy stamps. Pick up dry cleaning.
Don't let Phoebe in.
언제부터 마사지 받은 거야?
How long has this been going on?
- 알렉산드라가...
- 이름도 있어?
-Well, Alexandra has..
-It has a name?
피비, 화내지 마
Phoebe, don't get upset.
알았어, 이미 늦었어! 갈 거야
빨리 와, 챈들러
Okay. Oh, too late! I'm leaving.
Come on, Chandler, let's go.
그게 난...
Well, I thought I'd..
알았어
Yeah, what the hell.
프렌즈 시즌 8
'모니카의 비밀'
한 번 더 힘주는 거야
이제 거의 다 됐어
One more push.
Come on, we're almost there.
우리가 잘돼 아기를 낳다니
너무 행복해, 사랑해
I'm happy things worked out for us
and we're having this baby. I love you.
나도 사랑해
I love you too.
지금 이런 말하기엔 좀 그렇지만
I hope it's not
an inappropriate time to say..
자기 섹스는 최고야
you're the best sex I've ever had.
그런 건 늘 환영이야
That's always appropriate.
좋아, 한 번만 더 힘을 주는 거야
Okay, come on, one more push.
One more push.
됐어요
There we go.
두 분의 예쁜 아기예요
정말 축하 드려요
Here is your beautiful baby.
Congratulations.
친구 노릇 못한 놈이
아빠 노릇은 잘할까 몰라!
I hope you're a better father
than you are a friend!
조이!
Joey!
- 왜 그래?
- 내 배 좀 만져봐
-What's going on?
-Come feel my belly.
- 태동이 시작됐단 말야
- 정말?
-The baby's kicking for the first time.
-Really?
그래
Yes.
있잖아, 네가...
You know what? Maybe you..
네가 이쪽으로 와
밑에 아무것도 안 입었어
Maybe you should come to me.
I'm not wearing any bottoms.
세상에
Oh, my God.
너무 신기해!
It's unbelievable!
발길질이 심한게
그 누구냐...
Wow, she is kicking so much.
She's like..
그 짜증나는 여자 축구 선수
이름이 뭐지?
Who's that annoying
girl soccer player?
- 미아 햄?
- 미아 햄!
-Mia Hamm?
-Mia Hamm!
- 신기해
- 한 손으론 시트 잡아
-It's amazing.
-One hand on the sheet, Joe.
미안해
Sorry.
나 왔어
Hey, babe.
밥과 페이가 보낸 결혼 선물이야
우리를 싫어하나 봐, 그렇지?
We got a wedding gift from Bob and
Faye Bing. They don't like us, do they?
6불로 근사한 펀치 볼을
못 산다고 누가 그래?
Who says you can't get
a nice punch bowl for under $6?
- 가서 환불해
- 어디서 산 건지도 모르는데?
-Maybe we can take it back.
-Where would we return it?
창 밖으로 던져버리는 건 어때?
How about to the street,
from the balcony?
안돼, 그랬다 두 분이
우리 집에 오시면 어떡해?
We can't do that.
What if they come by for a visit?
15년간 얼굴 한 번 못 본
삼촌과 숙모가 불쑥 나타나
Let's cross that bridge when my aunt
and uncle who I haven't seen in 15 years..
펀치 볼을 보여달라고
잘도 그러시겠군
drop by unexpectedly and
demand a giant bowl of punch.
그냥 아무 데나 놔두면 안될까?
Why don't we just find a place for it?
찬장 어때?
In that cabinet?
거긴 깡통 넣어두는 데야
오리엔테이션 한 거 잊었어?
That's for canned goods. Have you
forgotten everything from orientation?
욕실 옆 창고 어때?
How about the closet by the bathroom?
- 좋아, 내가 넣어둘게
- 아냐, 내가 할게
-Okay. Let me do it.
-No, I'll do it.
가끔 이런 건 나한테 맡기고
마음 편하게 지내라구
You have to relax and let me
take care of things once in a while.
잠겼어, 도와줘
문은 왜 잠가놨어?
It's locked. You have to help me.
Why is it locked?
그냥, 내 개인 물건이 들었거든
No reason.
I keep private things in there.
이 집에 들어온 지 한참 됐는데
저 안은 한번도 못 봤어
I've been here a while,
and I've never seen what's in there.
뭐가 든 거야?
What is in there?
여성용품
Feminine stuff.
그런 말로 부끄럼 타게 하지 마!
Don't try to make me uncomfortable
with feminine stuff!
특별한 거 안들었어
날 사랑한다면 그냥 내버려 둬
Nothing in there concerns you.
If you love me, you'll just let it go.
- 알았어
- 고마워
-Fine.
-Thank you.
사랑해
Love you.
안녕, 챈들러, 날씨가 좋아
그리고 너
Hello, Chandler.
Lovely day, huh? You.
도움이 될지 모르겠는데
마사지 3년밖에 안받았대
If it helps, Alexandra's only
been massaging her for three years.
'모른다'고 했잖아
If! I said, if it helps.
왜 나한테 안받아?
Why won't you let me massage you?
어색하잖아, 넌 내 친구인데
네 앞에서 발가벗어야 하니 말야
I'd be self-conscious.
You're my friend. I'd be naked.
몇 년을 같이 살았어
너 벗은 몸도 봤다구
We lived together for years.
I've seen you naked.
그거랑은 다르잖아, 도대체 언제?
That's different. We were roommates.
And when?
인체에 호기심이 많은 것 뿐이야
I'm curious about the human body.
어색해하는 내 심정 이해하잖아
You can understand
why this would be weird.
난 프로야, 게다가 솜씨도 좋다구
I'm a professional
and I'm really good.
불편하면 더 이상 안 할께
기회를 줘, 부탁이야
If you're uncomfortable, we can stop.
Give me a chance. Please?
그 정도로 중요하다면
If it means that much to you.
중요해, 우리가 네 요리를
안 먹는다면 어떻겠어?
It does. How would you feel
if you couldn't share your cooking?
로스가 용에 대한 강의를
못하게 됐다고 가정해봐
Or how Ross would feel
if he couldn't teach us about dragons.
- 공룡이야
- 엎어 치나 메치나
-Dinosaurs.
-Potato, potahto.
로스, 태동이 시작됐어
Ross, the baby's kicking.
뭐? 정말?
What? It is?
지금은 아냐
It's not kicking now.
네가 이러는 걸
또 보고 싶긴 하지만 말야
Although we would love
to see you do that again.
언제 시작된 거야?
When? What happened?
어젯밤에, 태동을 느껴
조이한테 갔더니 자고 있더라구
Last night. I went into Joey's room,
and he was sleeping.
꿈도 안 꾸고
A dreamless sleep.
태동이 시작되다니 정말 근사해
My God, the baby's kicking.
That's great.
사실 아기 태동은 내가
제일 먼저 느껴보고 싶었는데
I wish I would have been there to feel
the kicking for the first time.
여길 만져봐, 태동이랑 비슷해
I got some stuff going on
if you want to feel.
됐어, 행복해 보이네
I'll pass, but you look radiant.
다음부턴 나한테 먼저 연락해
이거 내 호출기 번호야
I don't want to miss any more baby
stuff. Here's my pager number.
아기랑 관련된 건 뭐든 다 좋아
Anytime anything pregnancy-related
happens, use it.
새벽 3시도 괜찮아
아이스크림 사오라면 사 갈께
I don't care if it's 3 a.m.
and you want ice cream.
나한테도 좀 적어줄래?
Can I get a copy of that?
- 이불 덮었어?
- 그래
-Are you under the sheet?
-Yes.
좋아, 시작해
Great, let's begin.
강도가 어때?
How's the pressure?
좋아, 실력이 대단해
It's nice. Wow, Phoebe, you are good.
새삼스럽게, 고마워
Stating the obvious, but thank you.
- 어색하지 않지?
- 그래
-And it's not weird, is it?
-No.
그거야, 맘껏 즐겨
That's right, you just enjoy.
그래!
Oh, yeah!
- 그래!
- 알았어
-Oh, yeah!
-Okay.
세상에, 피비!
Oh, God, Phoebe!
바로 그거야! 그래, 바로 거기!
That's it! That's it, right there!
창고 열려고 안 했어, 정말이야
I wasn't trying to open
your closet, I swear.
모니카가 엄청 무서운가 보네?
뭐 하는 거야?
Monica runs a pretty tight ship here,
doesn't she? What are you doing?
모니카가 창고 안을 보여주질 않아
Monica has a secret closet.
She won't let me see it.
- 왜?
- 나도 몰라! 뭘 숨겨놓은 걸까?
-Why not?
-I don't know! What's she hiding?
나야 모르지
I don't know.
리처드가 분명해
I bet it's Richard.
- 뭐?
- 반박하기 전에
-What?
-Before you say I'm wrong..
내 질문에 대답해봐
let me ask you something.
리처드를 마지막 본 게 언제야?
When was the last time you saw him?
리처드를 왜 여기다 숨기겠어?
Why would she keep Richard in here?
내 직감인데
Off the top of my head..
케이크를 손에 쥔 걸로 모자라
먹기까지 하려는 거지
maybe she's having her cake
and eating it too.
'케이크'는 너고
'먹기까지'는 리처드야
You being the "cake,"
Richard being the "too."
- 그게 네 직감이라구?
- 그래
-That was off the top of your head?
-Yeah.
- 아니면...
- 또 시작이군
-Or..
-And here we go.
영화에서 봤는데 사람들이
문 뒤에 뭐가 있는지 궁금해서
I saw a movie where there was a door.
Nobody knew what was behind it.
마침내 그 문을 열었는데
엄청나게 많은 벌레가 나와서
When they finally got it open,
millions of bugs came pouring out..
사람들 살을 다 뜯어먹은 거야!
and they feasted on human flesh!
마누라 사생활 좀 지킨다고
어떻게 되지 않아!
It wouldn't kill you
to respect your wife's privacy!
창고에 벌레를 가둬놓을 게 뭐람!
Stupid closet full of bugs!
조이, 기분이 이상해
느낌이 이상한 게 아무래도...
Joey, something feels weird
and not good weird. I don't..
걱정 마, 누나들이 임신했을 때도
When my sisters were pregnant..
너랑 똑같은 말을 했는데
아무 일도 없었어
they got weird feelings
and it was always nothing.
- 정말?
- 물론이지
-Really?
-Absolutely.
그래도 만일을 대비해 병원에 가자
가는 길에 로스한테 호출 할께
But we'll stop by the hospital
just to be sure. I'll page Ross.
레이첼, 날 봐, 다 잘될 거야
날 믿어, 내 손을 잡아, 그렇지
Rach, look at me. Everything's fine.
Trust me. Take my hand. Here we go.
뼈 으스러진다!
Crushing bones!
병원에 잘 가는 거야
Good thing we're going to a hospital.
- 열려라, 열려
- 왜 문을...
-Open it.
-Why'd you..
조심해, 벌레 투성이야
Watch your feet.
There's bugs everywhere.
- 어때요?
- 괜찮습니다
-So?
-She's fine.
브랙스톤 힉스 수축이에요
자궁벽의 미세한 통증이죠
She had Braxton Hicks contractions.
Mild discomfort in the uterine wall.
미세해요? 브랙스톤 뭐시기를
직접 느껴본 적이 있나 봐요?
Mild discomfort? I take it you've had
one of these Braxton thingies?
- 다 정상인가요?
- 네
-Everything's normal?
-Yes.
- 아기도 무사하구요?
- 그럼요
-There's no danger?
-No.
무력감만 빼면 모두 정상입니다
Contractions can be unnerving,
but she's fine.
감사합니다, 선생님
침착하게 대처해줘서 고마워
Thank you, doctor.
And thank you for being nice and calm.
침착이라니!
무서워 죽는 줄 알았어!
I wasn't calm! I've never been
more scared in my life.
- 다 괜찮을 거라며?
- 누구 맘대로? 나 의사 아냐
-You said everything was okay.
-What do I know? I'm not a doctor.
- 어쨌든 다 잘됐어, 난 괜찮아
- 확실해?
-But everything is okay. I'm fine.
-You sure?
그래, 그 의사 자궁을
수축시킬까 하는 생각도 한걸
Yes. I got half a mind
to contract that doctor's uterus.
미세한 통증이라니!
자기가 어떻게 알아?
Mild discomfort!
What's he talking about?
- 모두 괜찮아?
- 그래
-Is everything okay?
-Yes.
병원으로 오라는 호출 받았어
어떻게 된 거야?
Your page said, "Come to
the hospital." What happened?
브랙스톤 힉스 수축이란 거래
Something called
Braxton Hicks contraction.
그거라면 걱정 마
대개의 여자들은 못 느껴
That's no big deal.
Most women don't feel them.
자궁 없인 언급을 말라
No uterus, no opinion.
그 사탕은 뭐야?
What's with the candy?
극장 매점에서 호출을 받았어
I was at the concession stand
at the movies.
- 혼자 영화 보러 갔었어?
- 모나!
-You went to the movies by yourself?
-Mona!
- 방에 잠깐 갔다 올께
- 왜 그래?
-I gotta go back in there.
-What's wrong?
- 무슨 일이 있어서가...
- 말해 봐, 무슨 일이야?
-I just gotta..
-No, really, tell me. What's up?
속옷 입는 걸 깜박했어
Look, I forgot my underwear.
레이첼을 데리고 와준 거 고마워
Thanks for bringing her to the hospital.
됐어, 별 일도 아닌데
Don't worry about it. No big deal.
내가 했어야 하는데 말야
아기 아빠는 나잖아
But still, it should have been me.
I'm the dad.
- 브랙스톤 힉스에 대한 자료예요
- 감사합니다
-Here's information on Braxton Hicks.
-Thanks.
병원에 데리고 온 건 잘한 겁니다
You did the right thing by bringing her in.
좋은 아빠가 될 거예요
You'll make a wonderful father.
이 친구만큼은 아녜요
사탕을 사왔잖아요
Hey, not as good as this guy.
He brought Twizzlers.
- 방법이 있을 거야
- 진정해, 커크 선장
-There has got to be a way.
-Easy there, Captain Kirk.
- 머리핀 있어?
- 그럼
-Do you have a bobby pin?
-Yeah.
잠깐, 난 9살짜리 여자애가 아냐
Oh, no, wait.
I'm not a 9-year-old girl.
근데 왜 그렇게 행동해?
Then why do you throw like one?
- 모니카한테 있을 거야
- 당연히 '모니카'겠지
-Maybe Monica has a bobby pin.
-Oh, sure, "Monica."
레이첼과의 부적절한 감정은
어떻게 돼가?
So how's the inappropriate
crush on Rachel coming?
아주 좋아, 언제라도
자살할 준비가 돼있어
Really good. I should be ready
to kill myself any day now.
금방 찾네
Well, you sure found that quick.
감정이 사라져줬으면 좋겠어
예전처럼 됐으면 좋겠다구
I wish I didn't feel this way about
Rachel. I wish things could be normal.
함께 사는 것도 너무 좋고
임신을 돕는 것도 너무 좋아
I love living with her, and
helping out with the baby is amazing.
로스가 소외감을
느낀다는 것만 빼면 말야
But now I think Ross feels left out.
레이첼과 병원에 갔을 때
의사가 날 아빠인 줄 알더라구
When I took Rachel to the hospital,
the doctor thought I was the father.
그때 로스 얼굴을 네가 봤어야 해
You should have seen
the look on Ross' face.
뭘 하는 건지 모르겠네
자물쇠가 더 단단해졌어
I have no idea what I'm doing.
For all I know, I'm locking it more.
- 신용 카드로 해봤어?
- 좋은 생각이야
-You try opening it with a credit card?
-That's a good idea.
로스가 소외감을 느낀단 말이지?
So Ross is kind of bummed, huh?
- 너무 미안해
- 네 잘못이 아냐
-I feel terrible.
-It's not your fault.
그렇다고 병원에 안 데려갈 거야?
넌 잘못한 거 전혀 없어
What are you gonna do, not take her?
You're doing nothing wrong.
로스의 아이를 임신한 여자를
넘본 것 말곤 말야
Except for harboring love
for the woman carrying his baby.
잘못한 거 있네
Well, there is that.
리처드, 혹시 거기 있다면
신용 카드 좀 건네주겠어?
Richard, if you're in there,
could you pass me my credit card?
어제는 정말 좋았어
네 마사지는 정말 최고야
I gotta tell you, yesterday was amazing.
That massage felt so good.
알고 있어
No, I got that.
- 매주 해주지 않을래?
- 좋아
-Can we make it a weekly appointment?
-Okay.
그런데 가격이 좀 올랐어
시간당 2백 불이야
You should know though,
I've raised my rates to $200 an hour.
- 좋아
- 아니, 5백 불
-Okay.
-I mean 500.
- 뭐?
- 6백
-What?
-600.
왜 그래?
What's going on?
마사지 받을 때
네가 신음 소리를 낸단 말야
You make sex noises
when you get massaged.
겁나 죽는 줄 알았어, 화가 나서
더 세게 했더니 완전 넘어가더라
It freaked me out. After a while,
I tried to hurt you. It spurred you on.
말도 안돼
난 신음 소리 낸 적 없어
You're crazy. There's nothing sexual
about the noises I make.
신음 소리가 아니라구?
There's nothing sexual about this?
세상에!
Oh, God!
뭘 봐요?
What are you looking at?
아니, 안녕
I mean, hi.
그래서 알렉산드라가 마사지를
할 때마다 귀마개를 꼈구나
Oh, that's why Alexandra wears earplugs
when she gives me a massage.
난 또 에냐를 싫어하는 줄 알았지
It's not because she hates Enya.
너무 창피해
다시는 마사지 안 받을 거야
This is embarrassing.
I'm never getting a massage again.
그렇다고 마사지를
포기할 것까진 없어
Don't let this stop you
from getting massages.
손님 중에 그런 사람 많은걸 뭐
I have lots of clients
that make those noises.
- 정말?
- 손님 말고 애인 중에
-Really?
-Well, not clients. Lovers.
다시 해보자
내가 고치도록 도와줄게
We'll try it again. Come back,
and we'll work through it.
- 정말이야?
- 그럼
-You sure?
-Yes.
- 알았어
- 좋아! 이제 실례 좀 할께
-I guess.
-Great! Now, if you'll just excuse me.
소리가 맘에 들었어요?
So did you hear something you liked?
로스, 이것 봐! 새로운 묘기야
Hey, Ross, check it out!
I learned a new trick.
바지 안에 손 집어넣어 봐
조이랑 똑같아질 걸
You know, if you stick one hand down your
pants, you're the spitting image of Joey.
점심 싸왔어
Hey, I brought you some lunch.
친절하기도 하셔라, 맛있겠네
Oh, that's so sweet of you. Oh, yum.
- 피클 넣었어?
- 그럼
-Did you put pickles on this?
-Well, yeah.
왜? 왜 그래? 레이첼, 왜 그래?
What? What? Rach, what?
- 왜 그래?
- 참치 샌드위치에 피클을 넣었어
-What's going on?
-I made her tuna with pickle.
피클? 피클 냄새 맡으면 구역질해
Pickle? Pickle makes her sick.
나한테 샐러드 주는 거랑 같다구
Giving her pickle is like giving me salad.
미안해, 그런 줄 몰랐어, 괜찮아?
I'm sorry, I didn't know. You okay?
괜찮아, 나 나가기 전에
누가 샌드위치 좀 치워줄래?
I'm fine, but someone make sure
it's gone when I get out?
알았어!
I'm on it!
나 때문에 레이첼이
구역질을 하다니
I shouldn't be the one making her throw up.
- 그럴 수도 있지 뭐
- 넌 이런 거 다 알고 있잖아
-lt could happen to anyone.
-Not to you. You know this stuff.
근데 애 아빠인 난 아무것도 몰라
I don't know any of it and I'm the father.
아빠 역할을 좀더 하고 싶단 말야
I wish I could be more involved, you know?
누가 메모 좀 해줘
난 이제 참치 안 먹는다고 말야
Well, if anyone is keeping score,
I no longer eat tuna.
둘이 나랑 잠깐 얘기 좀 할래?
Can I talk to you guys for a second?
- 그래
- 뭔데?
-Yeah.
-What's up?
앉아 봐, 우리 상황에 대해
얘길 하고 싶어
Sit down.
I wanna talk about our situation.
우리랑 헤어지려구?
Are you breaking up with us?
그러니까...
The thing is..
내가 레이첼과 함께 사니까
많이 관여하게 돼
because I live with Rachel,
I'm here for a lot of stuff.
반면 로스는 번번이
놓치고 말야, 그래서 말인데...
And Ross is missing everything. So..
그래서?
Yeah?
두 사람이 함께 사는 게 좋겠어
You two should live together.
나더러 나가라구?
나 여기 있는 거 싫어?
Are you asking me to move?
You don't want me here?
싫다니, 오히려 그 반대야, 다만...
No, I love living with you.
It just seems that..
룸메이트가 돼야 할 사람은
애 아빠라는 생각을 했어
if you're gonna have a roommate,
it may as well be the father.
하지만 로스는 나 때문에 사생활이
엉망이 되는 거 바라지 않을 거야
But, Joey, I don't think Ross wants me
to move in and disrupt his life.
바라나 보네
Or he does.
너랑 아기 가까이에 있고 싶어
I would love to be around
for you and the baby.
일단 시범적으로 해보는 거야
We can just try it,
like on a temporary basis.
- 하지만 우린 안 돼
- 연인으로서가 아니잖아
-But it's you and me.
-lt wouldn't be anything romantic.
난 모나랑 데이트 중인걸
젠장, 모나!
I'm dating Mona. Damn it, Mona!
1시간 전에 만나기로 했는데
나 왜 이러는 거지?
I was supposed to meet her
an hour ago. What is wrong with me?
그래, 어떻게 할래?
So, what do you think?
애 아빠랑 살다니 고리타분하네
Living with the father of the baby.
It's a little conventional for us.
내 아파트 늘 맘에 들어했잖아
Yeah, but hey, hey.
You always have liked my building.
게다가 구두 넣어둘 공간도
거기가 훨씬 더 많다구
And there's more room. I mean,
you could have a closet dedicated to shoes.
날 꿰고 있군
Oh, you do know your audience.
- 좀 그렇지 않아?
- 그렇긴, 천만에
-I don't know. Is it crazy?
-No.
조이, 멋진 생각이야
Joey, this is a smart idea.
멋지긴, 내가 좀 그래
Well, I was due.
- 좋아, 이사해
- 정말?
-Let's do it.
-Really?
레이첼, 잘 생각했어
Rach, that's great. That's great.
이사하는 거 손도 까딱 하지 마
And you know what?
Don't worry about any of the moving.
내가 다 알아서 할께
지금 당장 옮기는 거야
I'll take care of everything.
In fact, I'll start right now.
로스, 모나?
Ross, Ross. Mona?
왜 이러나 몰라
Unbelievable.
좋았어, 나 혼자 힘으로 해냈다구
Not too shabby.
I got this all off myself..
마누라 연장으로 말야
using my wife's tools.
맙소사
Oh, my God.
대체 어떻게 열었어?
How did you get in there?
지저분하네
You're messy.
- 아냐! 이건 보면 안 돼!
- 고물 박사랑 결혼했어
-No! You weren't supposed to see this!
-I married Fred Sanford.
챈들러, 이건 오해야
Chandler, you don't understand.
내가 얼마나
정리를 잘하는지 알지?
You know,
how I organize everything, right?
이건 분류가 안 되는 것만
따로 모아둔 거란 말야
Okay, well this is all of the stuff
that doesn't fit into any category.
그러니까 난 지저분한 게 아냐
So you see, I'm not messy.
정리를 잘하다 보니...
I'm just so organized that..
알았어, 알았다구!
다 사실이야, 난 지저분해
Okay, okay, fine! Now you know.
I'm sick.
아냐, 그렇지 않아, 내가 자기를
사랑하는 건 정리를 잘해서가 아냐
No, honey, you're not sick. I don't
love you because you're organized.
'정리를 잘함에도'지
I love you in spite of that.
정말?
Really?
- 비밀로 해줄래?
- 물론이지
-Promise you won't tell anyone?
-Yes.
그 대신 내 물건도
저기 넣어두면 안 될까?
Now that I know, if I've got extra stuff,
can we share the closet?
글쎄, 그게...
Well.. It's just..
그랬단 엉망이 될걸
I'm afraid you might mess it up.
- 조이
- 어서 와
-Hey.
레이첼이 이사했구나?
기분이 어때?
So Rachel's all moved out?
How you taking it?
맥주가 마구 고팠는데
I wanted to have a few beers..
레이첼이 냄새를 싫어해서
다 없애버렸더라구
but I got rid of those because
Rachel couldn't stand the smell.
대신 칼슘이 들어간
오렌지 주스를 들이켰어
I have thrown back a lot
of orange juice with calcium.
유효 기간이 몇 주 지난 거라
속이 많이 쓰리네
It's a couple weeks past its expiration
date, so it's got a bit of a kick.
- 괜찮아?
- 농담해? 끝내줘
-Are you okay?
-You kidding me? Yeah, I'm great.
끝내주는 정도가 아니지
견딜 만해
I'm better than great. I am good.
이제 레이첼이 없으니 그 동안
못했던 거 맘대로 할 수 있잖아
Now that she's gone, I can do stuff
around here that I couldn't do before.
가령...
Like..
발가벗은 채 활보를 한다든가
I can walk around naked again.
또는...
I can..
거실에서 포르노도 볼 수 있어
I can watch porn in the living room.
나한텐 잘된 거야
This is good for me.
난 혼자가 좋아
혼자서 더 잘 지내거든
I like being on my own.
I'm better off this way.
난 외로운 늑대야
I'm a lone wolf.
고독하지, 혼자야
A loner. Alone.
늘 혼자야, 영원히
All alone. Forever.
어떻게 해야 늑대 안아줄 거야?
What's a wolf gotta do
to get a hug around here?
좋아, 긴장 풀어
That's it, just relax.
- 자, 조금 더
- 맙소사!
-Come on, more.
-Oh, God!
맘에 드나 보구나?
You like that, don't you?
- 그래, 바로 거기야
- 여기? 얼마든지 해줄께
-Yeah, right there.
-Want it there? Take it there, baby.
- 피비?
- 그래, 내 이름을 불러, 어서
-Phoebe?
-Yeah, say my name. Say it.
이제 이불 덮어줄게
And now I'm going
to cover you back up.
몇 주 연락 안할 테니 찾지 마
And I won't be speaking with you
for several weeks.